[cheering]
[applause]
I'm not here.
>> Wait a minute. YOU WERE AT MY LAST SHOW.
>> LOOK, I get such little AFRICAN-AMEAN
AUDIENCE. I REMEMBER THE [\h__\h] from last
show.
A whole year has gone by. I'VE PLAYED
200 SHOWS. I SEE THE SAME BLACK GUY. OH
[\h__\h]
>> What is on your head?
>> You already did this to me the first
time you CAME HERE, MAN. OH [\h__\h] I DID.
YO, YOU YOU KNOW I'M TALKING TO YOU.
[laughter]
>> Last time you said, "What the [\h__\h] is
that?"
>> Bro, can I ask you something? What the
[\h__\h] is that?
[applause]
>> You have hair, here, and then nothing
here. Now, look, my dad is actually
Ethiopian, and my mom is from Texas, but
he's a special.
>> Are you distracting us from your
weirdass hairstyle?
Let me tell a story. My father, my
mother who was school professor, what
did that have to do with your hair?
[laughter]
No hair, bro. I see the [\h__\h] hair.
You left it there. You had the choice to
shave it. You're like, I'm going to with
everybody.
I'm going to go to every comedy show.
And when they pick on me, I'm like, my
father was a professor, Texas. My mother
was Mother Teresa.
Bro, can I ask you a question?
What's the situation down here?
Do you comb it over?
Only a black guy can pull that [\h__\h] off.
Come on, man. Let everybody see your
hair.
[cheering]
[applause]
Look at that. Look at that, man. Look
how cool he made his hair. It's not even
in the center. is like off center to the
right in the back. If this white guy did
it, it would look like he's got a
disease or some [\h__\h]
He does it every like, damn, MAN. YOU'RE
SO STYLISH. WHAT ARE YOU, A DESIGNER?
>> That's your mom?
>> Oh, she's beautiful. Where are you guys
from?
>> She got [snorts] divorced when you were
2, three years old. And did you ever
remarry, Mom?
>> You did how many times?
Just one more time and you're still
married.
>> Oh my god, that's amazing. Good for you.
[applause]
You only made one mistake in your life
and your daughter reminds you every day.
Is he white?
>> I can tell.
I can tell. Mom, you got good taste.
>> You're half You're half white. Oh,
you're from the new marriage.
>> No,
>> you're from the old [\h__\h]
Mom, no Korean ever. [laughter]
>> And you're gorgeous. You're really
stunning. Mom,
>> the first husband. Mom, spill the beans.
Mom,
>> Iranian. No.
[applause]
>> Wait a minute. So, you're half Korean,
half Persian?
>> No, I'm not.
your husband number two. Persian guy.
Well, he's smart. He pulled out.
He's like, "Yeah, never mind."
You're an executive for an insurance
company. What kind of insurance company?
>> Farmers.
>> Farmers. Oh, that [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
>> Do you think you can help me and bring
my quote down
with some sort of executive order that
you can put in?
Like
>> an executive coach?
>> You mean like an executive coach? Can
you coach the [\h__\h] agent that sold me
the sold me the plan?
Every year she calls me, "Oh my god, the
court's going to hire." [laughter]
And then there were fires in in in LA.
Now I have a house and I don't have
insurance.
Why? Because there's one tree next to my
house. [laughter]
The one tree has cost me $50,000 a year
for insurance.
>> I wish I could. I brought a gardener
with my neighbor Karen showed up. Oh my
god. Are you going to cut that tree?
It's living. I'm like, THIS TREE IS
COSTING ME $50,000.
IT'S LIKE, so what?
It cleans the air.
Do not touch it. I'm going to call the
cops.
So, I'm just waiting for the day Karen
dies across the street
so I can cut the goddamn tree and make
her coffin. [laughter]
So, I can make her coffin out of the
tree. [laughter]
Sorry, it was a bad dark joke for the
white girl. She goes, "I'm going to
die." [laughter]
>> Ethopia. Eopia.
>> Yes. Well,
>> it took you 6 years to see you.
>> No way.
>> It took you six Were you coming with a
with a boat or some [\h__\h] Were you
[\h__\h]
Were you canoeing over?
Where were you the last 6 years?
You were running [laughter]
from the mall.
Good to see you, my brother. And And
when did you move to the States?
>> It's been six years.
Bro, I just thought you got here.
>> You've been in the state for 6 years and
you didn't come see me?
>> You know what? I travel a lot for work.
That's why like I couldn't make it like
on your show. When I was in Ethiopia, I
was the biggest fan of yours. That's
why.
>> Really? So, you've been following me
since you lived in Ethiopia?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Ah, that's so cool, man. You came by
yourself tonight?
>> Oh, yeah, I did.
>> So, you're not with the Asian guy?
>> [laughter]
>> What about the ambiguous guy on your on
your right? I I don't know what the guy
on your right is. He looks like he could
be African. Uh he could be Mexican. He
could be Persian. He could be Greek. He
could That guy could be anything.
That guy could be I'm a Japanese. I'm
like, "Oh, okay. I believe you. You
Japanese." And what about your lady?
>> I'm Ethiopian.
>> Did you know you're going to sit next to
another Ethiopian?
>> I didn't.
>> Ah, this is great. I hate it. But you
know, God did.
>> God did.
>> This guy thinks God made this happen. He
doesn't know the theater seating chart
is racist.
This is kind of dangerous. You know, I
was very worried because I thought in
this climate we come here, we all
gather, eyes will be outside.
this guy. It took me six years to see
you and then we moved back to Ethiopia.
[laughter]
And you guys are together. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's so sweet. He's Persian. So
So you're like you're this the white
girl that's like I'm going to go and be
adventurous
and date something dangerous.
Let me see what's on Bumble.
Oh, Persian
sounds exotic.
Like the rug
they meet. He shows up with his belly
button, like his shirt open to his belly
button.
He's like, "Oh my god, he really has the
rug."
He's like, "I cannot wait to take you up
to kebab."
She's like, "Oh my god, he's going to
show me his kebab."
Meanwhile, this guy is at home making
kebab.
[applause]
>> Calling his mother, "Mother, I have a
beautiful white woman coming to my
house. How do I make kebab?"
Oh, you're getting married. Oh my god,
that's so cool. [applause]
This is unbelievable timing, isn't it?
As soon as I started uh getting people
out of the country, they decided to get
married. [laughter]
Thank you for doing this for us.
>> On behalf of the Persian community,
we're very grateful.
>> You like the Persian culture.
>> I love it.
>> Oh, you love it. What do you like about
it?
>> I love his family.
>> You love the family. So, his family is
very nice with you. Yeah. Wait till he
get his green card.
I'm just giving you heads up.
The family
is going to be up your ass.
Just letting you know. [applause] Wait
till he gets his passport. Holy [\h__\h]
He live with my mom.
>> You guys live with your mom. A You see,
that's the beauty of white families.
Yeah. Now, can you imagine if you lived
with his mom
every morning? Are you awake?
Honey, why you asleep too much? It's
6:00 a.m. You should be up already.
Come help me make breakfast. Today, I'm
going to teach you how to make food.
Did you iron my son's clothes?
What are you doing today? Where are you
going? I'm coming with you.
That's great, man. You're never going to
come to my show again, huh?
Trust me, if you survive this show, this
marriage is going to last a hundred
years.
[applause]
That's right.